https://www.hydravalve.co.uk/privacy/

Menu
Manual ValvesBall ValvesBrass Ball ValvesBronze Ball ValvesStainless Steel Ball ValvesCarbon Steel Ball ValvesCast Iron Ball ValvesPlastic Ball ValvesManual Ball Valves with Limit SwitchButterfly ValvesWafer Type Butterfly ValvesFully Lugged Butterfly ValvesHUK Butterfly Valve AccessoriesHUK Grooved End Butterfly ValvesPVC Butterfly ValvesHygienic Sanitary Butterfly ValvesHigh Performance Butterfly ValvesHigh Performance Butterfly Valves AccessoriesGate ValvesBrass and Bronze Gate ValvesStainless Steel Gate ValvesCast Iron Gate ValvesCarbon Steel Gate ValvesCast Iron Gate Valve AccessoriesGlobe ValvesScrewed Globe ValvesFlanged Globe ValvesKnife Gate ValvesUni-Directional Knife Gate ValvesBi-Directional Knife Gate ValvesCheck ValvesBrass Check ValvesStainless Steel Check ValvesCarbon Steel Check ValvesCast Iron Check ValvesPlastic Check ValvesBronze Check ValvesY StrainersScrewed Y StrainersFlanged Y StrainersPressure Reducing ValvesScrewed Pressure Reducing ValvesFlanged Pressure Reducing ValvesPressure Relief ValvesGresswell ValvesNABIC Pressure Relief ValvesBalancing ValvesScrewed Balancing ValvesFlanged Balancing ValvesTest PointsNeedle ValvesAll Needle ValvesAir Vent ValvesAll Air Vent ValvesFloat ValvesAll Float ValvesActuated ValvesPneumatic Actuated ValvesPrisma Pneumatic ActuatorsPrisma Actuated Brass Ball ValvesPrisma Actuated Stainless Steel Ball ValvesPrisma Actuated Plastic Ball ValvesPrisma Actuated Butterfly ValvesHaitima Pneumatic ActuatorsHaitima Actuated Brass Ball ValvesHaitima Actuated Stainless Steel Ball ValvesHaitima Actuated Cast Iron and
Carbon Steel Ball ValvesHaitima Actuated Butterfly ValvesYTC PositionersPneumatic Actuator AccessoriesPneumatic Actuated Knife Gate ValvesElectric Actuated ValvesRuB Compact Actuated Ball ValveJ+J Electric ActuatorsJ+J Actuated Brass Ball ValvesJ+J Actuated Stainless Steel Ball ValvesJ+J Actuated Butterfly ValvesValpes Electric ActuatorsSolenoid ValvesBrass Direct ActingBrass Servo AssistedActuation AccessoriesAll Actuation AccessoriesSteam ValvesSteam Isolation ValvesBall Valves for SteamGlobe Valves for SteamHigh Performance Butterfly Valves for SteamActuated Valves for SteamAngle Seat ValvesSteam Solenoid ValvesSteam Check ValvesAll Steam Check ValvesSteam Safety ValvesAll Steam Safety ValvesSteam Reducing ValvesAll Steam Reducing ValvesSteam TrapsSteam Float TrapsSteam Bi-Metallic TrapsSteam Thermostatic TrapsVacuum BreakersAll Vacuum BreakersSteam Air Vent ValvesAll Steam Air Vent ValvesSight GlassesAll Sight GlassesLevel GaugesAll Level GaugesFilterationY-StrainersSeparatorsControl ValvesSafety ValvesSeetru Safety ValvesSight Flow IndicatorsScrewed Sight Flow IndicatorsFlanged Sight Flow IndicatorsAncillariesMalleable Iron FittingsGalvanised Malleable Iron FittingsBlack Malleable Iron FittingsMalleable Iron accessoriesASTM A234 WPB Weld FittingsStandard Weight BS1640 FittingsSteel FlangesBS4504 PN16 FlangesBS4504 PN40 FlangesANSI150 FlangesANSI300 FlangesBS10 Table D/E FlangesStainless Steel 150lb FittingsBSP Threaded Stainless Steel 150lb FittingsGasketsKlingersil C4430 GasketsPlastic FittingsPVC Imperial Plain FittingsPVC Metric Plain FittingsPVC BSP FittingsPVC FlangesAccessories for Plastic FittingsPressure Gauges40mm Dial Pressure Gauges63mm Dial Pressure Gauges100mm Dial Pressure GaugesBolt SetsAll Bolt SetsExpansion BellowsFlanged Expansion BellowsOther Ancillary ProductsIndustrial Hose and FittingsFluid PowerPneumaticsAir PreparationPilot ValvesSilencersOne Touch Push-in FittingsPneumatic TubingFittings and AdaptorsInstrumentationNeedle ValvesPneumatic Pressure GaugesHydraulicsCompression FittingsHydraulic TubingHydraulic Hose and Fittings
Brands
Brands
Adler Spa
Brandoni
Buracco
Burkert
CH Coraplax (Aquaram)
CMO
Crane
Durapipe FIP
Ebro Armaturen
Enolgas
Genebre
Gestra
Goetze
Account
MERRY CHRISTMAS | An Extra 20% Off All Online Orders. Discount applied automatically at checkout. Offer ends 31/12/20.
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how this website uses and protects any information that you give while using this website. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What Personal Information do you collect?
When you browse our website or carry out actions such as the following:
Create a customer account
Place an order
Sign up to our mailing list or subscribe to any other services that we offer
Contact us, whether by phone, email or live chat
Then, we may collect your personal information, including:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone or mobile number
Payment information
Customer Service correspondence records
Technical information about how you access and use our websites, including your IP address, browser type, referring URL and operating system.
Cookies - for more information see below.
What is done with this information?
We use your information for the following:
To process your orders. We use relevant personal information described above (including your name, address and payment details) to process and deliver your order, process refunds and to notify you of the status of your order.
To provide Customer Support. If you contact our Customer Service, we will use your identification information to identify you and other personal information such as your order number to process your request and provide you with the best service possible.
To improve our website and services. We use your personal information to help analyse and understand how you use our products and services, to develop more interesting and relevant products and services, to improve our website, as well as to personalise the products and services we offer you.
Fraud Prevention. To prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our sites.
Marketing.  If you consent, we will use your information to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you. We ask for your consent, where required by applicable law, in order to use the contact details you have provided to us to send personalised marketing or retargeting communications. Please see below for more information on third parties and cookies used to provide these services.
How long will you keep my information?
Customer and order information will be kept securely on our system until you request to remove it.
Mailing List Subscriptions will remain active until you opt out
Cookies - We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. For the full list of cookies we collect, see the List of cookies we collect section at the bottom of this page.
Consent
How do you get my consent?
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your payment card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.
If we ask for your personal information for marketing purposes. For instance, to offer you special discounts, we will request for your permission, if it hasn’t been granted already.
How do I withdraw my consent?
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent to marketing communications. Marketing will be terminated and any data specifically used for marketing purposes alone will be deleted.
Financial transaction data will be maintained as required by law.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Cookie NameCookie Description
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
* Other third party cookies may be included from the following services;
Hydravalve (UK) is a trading division of Fluidpower Group UK LTD, Black Country House, Rounds Green Road, Oldbury, B69 2DG
website by Clickingmad
